<?xml version="1.0"?>
<items>
  
  <item>
    <itemid>1</itemid>
    <itemname>Marshall Hanwell Hi-Fi Speaker</itemname>
    <itemprice>400</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>A good pair of speakers are always more than welcome to any living room, especially if you are a huge lover of music. After all, music is food for the soul, where it is capable of elevating your emotions whenever you are down, or rousing your inner spirit to deliver courage and face whatever potential dangers and pitfalls that come your way. Well, for some much needed quality audio pumping through a compatible player, the $599.99 Marshall Hanwell Hi-Fi Speaker might just fit the bill perfectly.

This particular Marshall Hanwell Hi-Fi Speaker is extra special, since it comes branded with a numbered 50th Anniversary Edition commemorative badge apart from the standard capability of delivering quality audio, of course. One thing is for sure &#x2013; if you are someone who loves to live out a wireless lifestyle, then the Marshall Hanwell is not the Hi-Fi speaker for you, as it caters for this particular group that cares more about quality sound than about losing the wires. These are not exactly the most portable speakers in the world, either, since it tips the scales at a whopping 23 lbs., but when your ears greet the sound, you know for sure that it is well worth the effort in dropping some serious coin for it. You can now have the classic rock Marshall concert experience in your living room with the room-filling audio capable Marshall Hanwell Hi-Fi Speaker. To roll back the years even more, it comes with analog controls for volume, bass and treble in addition to a classic power switch. </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/marshallhifispeaker.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>12</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>6</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>2</itemid>
    <itemname>Sense bike light</itemname>
    <itemprice>600</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>Cycling is no doubt a healthy habit and a kind of exercise which is gaining popularity in many cities around the world. It has also been touted to be one way in reducing massive traffic gridlocks as cities which were built a long time ago did not anticipate the massive growth in population, so much so that the fast growing number of cars and SUVs have contributed their fair share of traffic jams. Well, if you love cycling, that is fine and dandy, but do make sure that you have the adequate amount of protection as you can never tell just what the future might bring. Increasing your visibility at night or in low light conditions are also important, which is why the See.Sense bike light might be a useful addition to your arsenal of cycling devices. </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/seesensebikelights.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>391</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>0</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>3</itemid>
    <itemname>iPin Laser Presenter</itemname>
    <itemprice>350</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>I am not quite sure about you, but when it comes to making a presentation, there are some essential tools that one will have to take into consideration. One, you will need to make sure that the venue has a projector which is bright enough to ensure everyone in the presentation hall will be able to get a good look at what you are trying to convey to them, and two, a laser presenter which makes it a whole lot easier to point out certain areas on the presentation screen to the audience. Just like how not all headphones are created equal, you have the award winning iPin laser presenter which will be able to turn your iPhone into a professional laser presenter. </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/ipinlaserpresenter.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>394</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>1</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>4</itemid>
    <itemname>HiFi Digital Music Player with built-in AMP/DAC </itemname>
    <itemprice>400</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>I know that times are still difficult for a fair number of people in the world at the moment, as the economy is not really picking up in the manner that most of us would like it to. Having said that, the eternal search fro the best bargains possible continue, even when it comes to the highly competitive tech sector. For those who want a digital audio player that delivers when it comes to sound quality, I guess things do not really get any better other than the $199.99 X3 HiFi Digital Music Player.

This puppy will be able to offer lossless playback from a digital audio player, where among the bevy of audio formats supported include WAV, APE, FLAC, MP3, WMA, OGG, ALAC(M4A), AAC, AMR, and MP2. Tell, your Star Trek loving audiophile that &#x201C;resistance is futile&#x201D; when it comes to adding to their collection of audio enhancing products and devices. The 3,000mAh lithium ion battery is touted to offer a wee bit more than 10 hours of non-stop playback, and best of all is, you will be able to perform a recharge using the included microUSB cable. All purchases will feature a silicone case, a couple of additional screen protectors, a co-ax converter cable, and a manual.  </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/hifidigitalmusic.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>397</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>0</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>5</itemid>
    <itemname>Philips and Sharp show</itemname>
    <itemprice>350</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>Both Royal Philips N.V. and Sharp Corp have come up with a 85-inch 8k4k naked-eye 3D LCD display which is guaranteed o wow the masses, as it was recently exhibited over at the FPD International 2013 that recently concluded in Yokohama, Japan. This particular joint venture saw Sharp develop the key technologies behind the 8k4k display, while Philips played a role in introducing its own lenticular lens that has been mounted on its surface in order for 3D video to be viewed with but the naked eye. Philips did consider using the display for digital signage purposes, but the folks over at Sharp claimed that they have yet to decide on a firm decision when it comes to commercialization. </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/philipssharp.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>396</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>1</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>6</itemid>
    <itemname>Zapi Toothbrush Sanitizer</itemname>
    <itemprice>350</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>Most of us would just leave our toothbrushes in a glass once we&#x2019;re done cleaning our pearly whites after each meal. Unfortunately, whenever you are not around, or when you are fast asleep through the night, that might just be when them pesky roaches come up to play. Cockroaches, as we all know, are extremely filthy creatures, carrying all sorts of bacteria with them on their vile bodies, and the thought of having it crawl all over your toothbrush is revolting. Hence, some of us have toothbrush containers that cover up the bristles, but paranoid androids out there can always pick up the &#xA3;24.99 Zapi Toothbrush Sanitizer.

You can choose from two different models &#x2013; Hi-Ya Ninja and an Owl, and I am quite sure that there is a very good reason for having both caricatures since owls do not sleep at night, symbolizing that they are watching over your toothbrush, while ninjas are just plain stealthy and double up as a great bodyguuard to your toothbrush. The Zapi Toothbrush Sanitizer works this way &#x2013; just insert your toothbrush, press the button and the Zapi will do its best to remove all possible germs, bacteria and viruses, making sure that it is ready to give your teeth a nice enamel scrubbing session. The UV light of the Zapi Toothbrush Sanitizer will stay on for 6 minutes once it has turned on.  </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/zapi.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>398</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>1</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>7</itemid>
    <itemname>Electronic Singing Sunflower </itemname>
    <itemprice>45</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>Plants vs Zombies 2 has just been released on the Android platform long after folks with iOS devices have had their fair share of game time with that mobile game, so here is a little something for you to show off your pent up interest in this game by picking up the $29.99 Plants vs. Zombies Electronic Singing Sunflower. Yes sir, sunflowers in the Plants vs. Zombies game are essential to keeping the zombie horde at bay, as you will then be able to amass enough sunlight so that you can shore up your defenses.&#xD;
&#xD;
The musical score or ditty in the Plants vs. Zombies game must have had quite an impression on many folks, as there is nothing quite like a catchy tune in order to make a particular gme title all the more addictive and appealing. Needless to say, the Plants vs. Zombies Electronic Singing Sunflower is not recommended for outdoor use, but rather, it will sit pretty on your desk while playing the &#x201C;There&#x2019;s a Zombie on Your Lawn&#x201D; tune and dancing along. It might just make you take a glance out of the window, in case there is actually a zombie that is bearing down on you for your perfectly healthy brain. No photosynthesis is required here, as the Plants vs. Zombies Electronic Singing Sunflower would be powered by a trio of AA batteries instead. </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/singingsunflower.gif</imgsrc>
    <qty>298</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>1</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>8</itemid>
    <itemname>Traveler&#x2019;s Mold And Bacteria </itemname>
    <itemprice>60</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>When one travels, there are plenty of things to take into account, especially when it comes to packing your stuff. It is always advisable to leave a list of items that you need to cram into your suitcase, so that nothing goes missing. Checklists are useful at all times, only as long as they are used properly. Some of us are poor travelers, and as such, we need to pack more &#x201C;comfort&#x201D; items. Case in point, if you have an extremely sensitive nose, then the $199.95 Traveler&#x2019;s Mold And Bacteria Reducing Air Purifier would definitely come in handy.

As it stands, the Traveler&#x2019;s Mold And Bacteria Reducing Air Purifier is a pocket-sized air purifier which claims to reduce both mold and bacteria in the air or on surfaces. The device itself would rely on a similar technology that was developed by NASA for air purification aboard spaces shuttles. There will be an ultraviolet light inside the device which combines with a nickel catalyst, where it will then be able to emit safe catalytic molecules which destroy up to 99% of mold and bacteria in five hours. Since you are traveling, you do not need to tote about anything bulky, which is why this device measures roughly the size of a radar detector, allowing you to set it up unobtrusively. It is a filterless design, so there is no need to replace filters replacements from time to time. </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/travellersmoldandbateria.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>295</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>2</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>9</itemid>
    <itemname>JBL Pulse</itemname>
    <itemprice>60</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>&#x201C;Party like there is no tomorrow!&#x201D; would have been one of the mantras of the younger ones out there, especially in this day and age where most of us want things instantly, without having to &#x201C;pay our dues&#x201D; first. You know what they say, if you want to get something done, do it yourself, and do it correctly. Hence, if you are the regular socialite in your neighborhood and love throwing parties like the Great Gatsby himself, then you would surely need more than an extravagant home. Harman has something special for you that comes in the form of the JBL Pulse, with it being described as being able to &#x201C;change the way you enjoy music.&#x201D; Ah well, there is only one particular way to find out whether that is true or not, and that would be to purchase a set yourself.

Just how does the JBL Pulse work? Well, it will firstly ensure that your favorite tunes will be heard, but what&#x2019;s more interesting is, it will also ensure that your party would be the best in the neighborhood since you will also be seen. Imagine a lightshow that is perfectly synchronized in brightness, alongside the color. That would definitely be something worth checking out ,wouldn&#x2019;t it?

The JBL Pulse is said to offer gives music that is not only heard, but &#x201C;seen&#x201D;, as it merges room-filling JBL sound with an eye-catching, programmable LED light show, all crammed into a tiny portable speaker. You can now bring your favorite tunes with you wherever you go, while enjoying a multi LED light show to boot. To make sure that the JBL Pulse keeps up with the times, it comes with wireless connectivity, streaming your music from any portable device via Bluetooth. The battery of the JBL Pulse itself can deliver up to 10 hours of musical playback wirelessly, or half that amount of time if you want to include a music and light show. Be prepared to fork out $199 for this puppy  </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/jblpulse.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>295</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>2</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>10</itemid>
    <itemname>SwitchEasy Tanks Battery </itemname>
    <itemprice>60</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>When we get about three quarters through our day, most of our gadgets are starting to gasp for breath. By the end of the work day, they&#x2019;ll be at 1% or worse if we don&#x2019;t take any action. While it&#x2019;s best to have a charging option available at your desk, there&#x2019;s nothing wrong with wanting to have a backup battery handy.  </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/SwitchEasyTanks.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>299</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>0</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>11</itemid>
    <itemname>Baladeo 52G Pocket Cutlery </itemname>
    <itemprice>60</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>If you happen to be someone who loves tinkering around with stuff, and have amassed quite a collection of Swiss Army Knives over the years, then you would definitely fall in love with the $59.99 Baladeo 52G Pocket Cutlery Set. Why do I say this? That is because it has just about everything that you need whenever the dinner bell rings, and you go off to satiate that hunger of yours. The Baladeo 52G Pocket Cutlery Set can be said to be more or less &#x201C;complete&#x201D;, as all the utensils within it have been forged from 420 stainless steel for that added mark of quality.

This is an ultralight cutlery set which will feature five functions that have been wrapped up into a single small, good looking package. You will find a spoon, fork, knife, can opener, and bottle opener within, where all of the pieces will fold and lock together in order to be carried in its mesh carrying case. You can also open it up with a few steps so that it would function as a cutlery set. Best of all is, it has been specially made for travel purposes, so you can ensure that it will be temperature resistant (within reasonable limits, I am quite sure that even it is unable to withstand the fires of Mount Doom when tossed there).   </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/pocket_cutlery.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>298</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>1</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  
  <item>
    <itemid>12</itemid>
    <itemname>LG Nexus 5  </itemname>
    <itemprice>60</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>Well, well, what do we have here? Yet another high end smartphone that has hit the market? This time around, it is the Android flag that is being flown high, thanks to the folks over at Google who have partnered with LG. Hopefully following the successful footsteps of its predecessor, the LG Nexus 4, the LG Nexus 5 would be the first smartphone in the world that will run on the Android 4.4 KitKat mobile operating system. Not only that, this particular handset would come with its fair bit of features, in addition to being the slimmest and fastest Google Nexus phone to date. </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/nexus5.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>298</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>0</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>13</itemid>
    <itemname>Screwdriver Programmable TV   </itemname>
    <itemprice>60</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>Are you a huge fan of your sports team, or you have a famous TV or movie series that you simply cannot get enough of? That would most probably mean you have amassed quite a collection of memorabilia to date, ranging from T shirts to coffee mugs, toys and other forms of collectibles. Well, Doctor Who fans will definitely fall in love with the $99.99 Exclusive 10th Doctor Sonic Screwdriver Programmable TV Remote.

The name of this particular device itself says it all &#x2013; you will be able to gain control of your TV just like the 10th doctor, with this being a gesture-based universal remote control. It is made out of CNC-machined aerospace aluminum metal parts, so you can be sure that the quality of this TV remote itself will rank pretty high up there. Based on David Tennant&#x2019;s sonic screwdriver, this is a gesture-based, fully-functioning, programmable infrared remote control, letting you handle the plethora of devices which sit in your living room entertainment area without batting an eyelid. With three memory banks, it is capable of recognizing up to 39 gestures in total. Each purchase would come with a microUSB charging cable to juice up its rechargeable battery whenever it starts to run low in power.  </itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/screwdriver_remote.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>297</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>0</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>14</itemid>
    <itemname>Boogie Board</itemname>
    <itemprice>45</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>What does it take these days to capture the attention of your young ones? Well, it does seem as though you will need something that is louder and brighter, with most probably some battery power required to deliver the amount of multimedia capability that can capture the imagination of the masses. Pen and paper? That is pretty much an archaic idea by now, but if you want to introduce them to the joys of drawing and doodling without having to cut down any more trees, then the &#xA3;19.99 Boogie Board Jot 4.5 LCD eWriter would fit the bill nicely.&#xD;
&#xD;
The Boogie Board Jot 4.5 LCD eWriter would arrive in a choice of blue, pink and red shades, making it an eco-friendly electronic alternative to paper. Not only that, since it is meant to be used by kids, it is no surprise then, to see it arrive with a shatter-proof Reflex LCD screen. Not only that, Boogie Board claims that it is good for up to 50,000 erases, which roughly translates to approximately 7 to 10 years on average, which by then your little one would have outgrown it a long time ago. Each Boogie Board Jot 4.5 LCD eWriter would come with a stylus that is stashed away on the side for easy portability.</itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/screwdriver_remote.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>100</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>0</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  <item>
    <itemid>15</itemid>
    <itemname>Bluetooth speaker</itemname>
    <itemprice>200</itemprice>
    <itemdesc>When it comes to high quality portable speakers, there are many names out there in the market. The thing is, the selection process can be rather tricky &#x2013; so why not pick one from Soundmatters? The name of the company itself is pretty self-descriptive, as Soundmatters was founded by former NASA engineer/audio legend Dr. Godehard Guenther. Recently, they announced that they will be shipping what is deemed to be the world&#x2019;s slimmest, lightest high-fidelity Bluetooth Speaker, simply known as the DASH7.</itemdesc>
    <imgsrc>productImages/soundmatters-dash7.jpg</imgsrc>
    <qty>98</qty>
    <qtysold>0</qtysold>
    <qtyonhold>1</qtyonhold>
  </item>
  
</items>
